{
    "subject": "resource/International_Surf_Lifesaving_Association",
    "predicate": "property/content",
    "object": "Huntington Beach, California, USA",
    "human_readable": "The content of International Surf Lifesaving Association is located at Huntington Beach, California, USA.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9353036284446716,
            "question": "Where is the International Surf Lifesaving Association located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9202869534492493,
            "question": "Where in the United States is the International Surf Lifesaving Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8874258995056152,
            "question": "Which US location serves as the base for the International Surf Lifesaving Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.882992684841156,
            "question": "What city in California hosts the International Surf Lifesaving Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8628566861152649,
            "question": "What is the address of the International Surf Lifesaving Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8387485146522522,
            "question": "Where can you find the headquarters of the International Surf Lifesaving Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7968228459358215,
            "question": "What city is known for hosting the International Surf Lifesaving Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7913413047790527,
            "question": "In what country is the International Surf Lifesaving Association headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7779450416564941,
            "question": "What state is home to the International Surf Lifesaving Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46408185362815857,
            "question": "Is the International Surf Lifesaving Association located in Europe?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The content of International Surf Lifesaving Association is located at Huntington Beach, California, USA.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3127_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is home to the International Surf Lifesaving Association?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3127_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country is the International Surf Lifesaving Association headquartered?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3127_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is known for hosting the International Surf Lifesaving Association?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3127_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3127_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3127_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3127_154.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3127_159.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3127_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3127_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3127_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3127_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3127_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3127_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states the ISLA's headquarters are in Huntington Beach, CA, but doesn't specify that the *content* is located there.  It's likely referring to their operational base or offices. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context information, the International Surf Lifesaving Association (ISLA) has a website http://www.islasurf.org and is described as being based on a global level, with no mention of a specific location such as Huntington Beach, California, USA."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n- The documents provide information about the International Surf Lifesaving Association (ISLA) and its headquarters being in Huntington Beach, CA. However, they do not state that the content of ISLA is located there. The term \"content\" here seems to be misinterpreted or incorrectly applied; the documents describe activities and goals rather than physical content storage locations.\n- Therefore, based on the provided context information, the statement cannot be confirmed as correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}